[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "We call visible light the electromagnetic radiation belonging to the what wave range?", "correct_answer": "380-750 nm", "incorrect_answers": ["12,000-15,000 nm", "1000-1500 nm", "100-520"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "On which continent is the geographic region of Central America located?", "correct_answer": "North America", "incorrect_answers": ["Central America", "South America", "All of these"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these statements is true about the Black garden ant?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["Each colony has only one queen.", "It is found in Europe.", "It is found in North America and Asia."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which statement about elephants is untrue?", "correct_answer": "Elephants do not have great memories", "incorrect_answers": ["Elephants sleep standing up", "Elephants cry", "There are some pink elephants in India"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What does ADSL stand for?", "correct_answer": "Asymmetrical Digital Subscriber Line", "incorrect_answers": ["Asynchronous Digital Subscriber Line", "Asynchronous Dial-up Subscriber Line", "A Darn Slow Lan"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This model turned actress died a horrible death in the movie Malone. Malone, played by Reynolds, got even and made sure that her murderer died the same way.", "correct_answer": "Lauren Hutton", "incorrect_answers": ["Cindy Crawford", "Cynthia Gibbs", "Lauren Bacall"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "If youve ordered a burn one, take it through the garden, pin a rose on it, what can you expect to be placed in front of you?", "correct_answer": "Hamburger with Lettuce, Tomato and Onion", "incorrect_answers": ["Hot Dog with Chili and Coleslaw", "Lamb Shish - Kabob", "Tuna Melt on Rye with Lettuce and Dill Chips"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "I tried to run away, but I couldnt get far due to my agyrophobia. What was I afraid of?", "correct_answer": "Crossing roads", "incorrect_answers": ["Getting a muscle cramp", "Grass", "Driving"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What does NP mean in instant messaging language?", "correct_answer": "no problem", "incorrect_answers": ["noogie patrol", "no parents", "new puppy"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the Hellraiser series, in order for Pinhead to be summoned, one should do what?", "correct_answer": "open a puzzle box", "incorrect_answers": ["dial a 7-digit number and say \u201cI call you! Come now!\u201d", "spell out his name five times in front of a mirror", "break the spell that keeps him in Hell"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Nails appear on fingers and toes during the 18th week of the development of a fetus.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What animals does malacology study?", "correct_answer": "Mollusks", "incorrect_answers": ["Jellyfish", "Monotremes", "Arthropods"]}]